Xiao Fen
Last time you asked on the YouTube channel
Which type of oil do people prefer
to use for stir-frying?
Olive oil is the most commonly used.
65% of their fans
use olive oil
13% of people use Camellia seed oil.
Some people also use lard to cook.
Hey, in that case
Camellia seed oiland olive oil
Its strength is truly formidable.
I remember that
many mothers would take
Camellia seed oil
during their postpartum period
Hey, Camellia seed oilisn't just for postpartum women!
People our age
should eat good oil
Take care of your spleen and stomach
Take care of your heart and brain
tell you how to eat it right away.
Hu Naiwen is about to begin his lecture.
I am your old friend, Dr. Hu.
Not eating oil, skin has been bad for 20 years.
One food actually improved
Did you know?
What happens if you lack fat in the long term?
Skin will not only become
dry, rough, and itchy
Even aging faster
than their peers
Let me give you two real-life examples.
Entrepreneur Wei Boss
She once shared
on her channel
Her friend wanted to lose weight.
Do not eat fried food
Even vegetables need to be rinsed.
don't even dare to use skincare creams.
As a result,skin became so dry
that white powder would flake off whenever scratched it.
The skin flakes are coming out.
dandruff has also increased.
Wow
Wow, hearing this example...
It's so scary.
Being thin won't make beautiful.
Low oil content
may cause skin ulceration
I once
did a TV program
with Dr. sòng yàn rén (transliteration)
He then shared the story of one of his patients.
have been a vegetarian for 20 years and haven't touched a single drop of oil.
Skin ulcers that have persisted for years and cannot be cured
Later, I heard from Dr. Song that
The body needs fat.
to eat a few slices of pork belly
After a week,
skin actually returned to normal
I'll share a...
Taiwan's national treasure oil
It's called Camellia seed oil
It is the seed of the Oil-seed Camellia
The oil extracted
It's just as good as olive oil!
Is Camellia seed oil a good oil?
What are the health benefits
of Camellia seed oil?
tell you right away
Drinking this in the morning
nourishes the stomach, promotes bowel movements, and prevents periodontal disease
We all know that olive oil
can be consumed directly
Camellia seed oil
Can we drink it directly?
Can
There are two types of Camellia seed oil
Great way to use
Rinse mouth and drink directly
Before brushing your teeth in the morning
You can rinse your mouth with a little Camellia seed oilfirst.
It's called Oil Pulling
It is an oral hygiene method
that has been passed down in India for thousands of years
It has many benefits!
Can prevent periodontal disease
Reduce gum redness and swelling
The mouth is healthier
How to do it
Before brushing your teeth in the morning
Gargle with 10 to 15 cc of Camellia seed oil
It will take about 10 minutes.
Then spit the oil onto the toilet paper.
At this time
Do you know
what happens when you spit oil onto toilet paper?
milky white
This means that bacteria and impurities, etc
are brought out.
Rinse your mouth with clean water again.
Then brushing your teeth will finish.
Oh, I've tried it.
I added Camellia seed oil
Rinse your mouth with it
It feels very gentle
This method
What are its effects?
Camellia seed oil
contains natural antioxidants.
Tea polyphenols
And Vitamin E
You use it to rinse your mouth
Reduce gum inflammation
Make mouth healthier
The second one is drinking Camellia seed oil raw.
Doctor, when is the best time to drink Camellia seed oil?
How much should drink?
Take one tablespoon on an empty stomach in the morning
But my key is very small.
This spoon probably contains less than 2cc.
Therefore, should use five to six spoonfuls
of this spoon.
This kind of Camellia seed oil
is quite good.
You will gain two major benefits
First, it lubricates the intestines and promotes bowel movements.
Second, nourish the stomach and protect the stomach wall.
Drinking water is not enough to have a smooth bowel movement.
Drink Camellia seed oil on an empty stomach in the morning
Helps you eliminate waste from your body
Everything goes smoothly all day long
Everyone is comfortable.
The second benefit
Some people may ask, is Camellia seed oil
really good for the stomach?
Camellia seed oil contains monounsaturated fatty acids
and tea polyphenols
It can form a protective
film in the stomach
Reduce stomach acid irritation
Can people with stomach pain, acid reflux
or stomach ulcers
drink Camellia seed oil?
Are there any side effects?
Can
Camellia seed oil
is a mild plant oil
stomachache
Gastroesophageal reflux
People with stomach ulcers
Consume a moderate amount of bitter tea oil in the morning.
Helps form a protective film on the stomach wall
Soothe acidic irritation
It's a great way to soothe your stomach.
However,
if you have severe acid reflux...
suggest you don't drink it on an empty stomach.
It may stimulate gastric acid secretion.
It's better for your stomach to eat it as a topping.
Camellia seed oil is more suitable
for older folks like us.
Because of our digestive power
It's not that good anymore.
The spleen and stomach functions are also relatively weak.
Camellia seed oil is good for the stomach,
easy to digest, and non-irritating.
Wow, this method!
Elders can try it
at home!
It's really practical.
And feel at ease
I really want to recommend it
to my parents
Third Uncle
Fifth Aunt
People who drink oil or rinse their mouths on an empty stomach in the morning
You can leave us a message
Tell us your experience!
Eat these oils
if you have heart discomfort to protect your heart and stabilize your blood pressure
Hey, you know what?
This kind of fluctuating weather
What most afraid of?
I'm most afraid of catching a cold.
With the economy so bad right now
if you
accidentally catch the flu
you'll have to spend money
on medical treatment
It's not worth it.
That's right
It's not just the flu.
Not warm enough
Sometimes the heart is also stimulated.
Causes myocardial infarction
stroke, etc.
Especially if you or your family have
High blood pressure, high blood sugar, and high cholesterol, and cardiovascular diseases
You must also protect your heart.
First move
Massage acupoints to strengthen the heart
Nèi guān (transliteration) acupoint is very powerful!
It simultaneously soothes discomfort in the heart, stomach, and chest.
Relieve chest tightness
arrhythmia
Prevention of myocardial infarction
At the same time, it eliminates bloating in the stomach.
Where is the Nèi guān (transliteration)acupoint?
Come, lend me your hand.
Three fingers above the wrist crease
Between these two tendons on the wrist
This is the Nèi guān (transliteration)acupoint.
Press it once a day
Protect your heart, chest, and stomach together.
Second move
How to eat to protect your heart
Eat healthy fats to protect your heart
The simplest lazy method
Just a bowl of noodles
Pour in the Camellia seed oil
Mix them like this
Hey, this is heartwarming, warming, and stomach-warming!
Get it done in one go
Camellia seed oil has two great substances
Tea polyphenols
Camelliaside
Tea polyphenols have antioxidant properties
Lower bad cholesterol
Camelliaside
It can lower blood lipids and reduce inflammation.
Protect blood vessels
I remember when I was a child
Grandma also uses
Camellia seed oil to stir-fry vegetables.
That Camellia seed oil
Can it withstand high temperatures?
Of course
Camellia seed oil can withstand high temperatures
200 to 250 degrees is no problem
It's even higher than
olive oil's 190 degrees
You want to use it to
Frying, boiling, stir-frying, deep-frying, mixing
Anything is fine
Convenient and safe cooking
We have many fans
They all use Camellia seed oil
to stir-fry vegetables
This Camellia seed oil
and olive oil
Which one is better?
They're all great!
Evenly matched
Choose based on your preferred use.
Bitter tea oil has a high smoke point
It is very suitable for Chinese cuisine.
Stir-frying over high heat is fine.
Olive oil has a very refreshing flavor.
You use it for cold dishes and salads.
It's pretty good, isn't it?
Oh, I did some research.
These two oils
They all seem to be good for cardiovascular health
right?
That's right
These are all good oils rich
in monounsaturated fatty acids.
Especially Camellia seed oil
Up to 79% Omega-9
Higher than olive oil
Helps blood flow smoothly
It can stabilize blood pressure and blood sugar.
Reduce the risk of blockage in blood vessels
So you are a person with hyperlipidemia
Drinking Camellia seed oil is great!
Comparable to olive oil
Top-quality oil certified by the beauty industry
Our pride of Taiwan: Camellia seed oil
It has excellent moisturizing power.
It's become popular overseas.
Japan's beauty industry
It is widely recognized as a top-quality oil
for skin and hair care
Like the super famous Japanese
camellia oil shampoo
It uses Camellia seed oil
The Japanese even call it
Camellia oil
Xiaofen, why don't you give it a try?
ok
It seems to have a nutty aroma
The aroma of the fruit
Okay, let me apply it and see.
It seems to be absorbed quite well
Right
Camellia seed oil is very similar
to the oils secreted by humans
It is easily absorbed
by the skin
Yeah, that's great!
Wouldn't it be great
if we added it
to our skincare products?
It should be great!
want to nourish myself but I'm afraid it will cause internal heat.
Camellia seed oil for nourishment
Wounds heal quickly
The dishes you cook for postpartum recovery
What kind of oil should use?
Are you a fan of Camellia seed oil
or sesame oil?
Leave a message and tell me.
How do you cook and eat at home?
We have
an editing colleague
She really likes camellia oil.
She said she would use camellia oil specifically for cooking
when helping her daughter-in-law during her postpartum period
Give her
This is a gentle tonic that won't cause internal heat.
Very good. Camellia seed oil is more gentle than sesame oil.
Did you know?
Sometimes I cook fish soup
Use this too.
Oh, that's pretty good too
you don't have to worry about getting overheated
Your home
Some had surgery
some were physically weak
People with chronic diseases
or anemia
Both are suitable
Don't worry aboutzào rè (transliteration)
No need to worry about getting pimples
Another effect
Add a little Camellia seed oil
when you stir-fry your vegetables
In addition to enhancing the fragrance
it can also relieve the tightness of wounds
Reduce pain
and aid tissue repair
Dr. Hu, I want a whole jar
of that Camellia seed oil
One bill is worth 6 (slip of the tongue)
Why is Camellia seed oil so expensive?
Because it's very precious
Camellia seed oil comes from this tea tree.
It's called yóu chá shù (transliteration)
Its fruit
Because its fruit is the Camellia seed
Extracted from this thing
There is only one harvest season per year.
From flowering to fruiting
It will take about 10 to 12 months.
Almost a year
Camellia seed oil is not like soybean oil.
Unlike peanuts
Unlike sunflower seeds
which have an oil yield of up to 40%
100 kg of Camellia seed
The maximum yield is 25 kilograms of oil.
That means it has only a 25% oil yield
Because the raw materials are scarce
the oil is purer
Of course the price has to be high.
That's really precious!
Did you enjoy today's sharing?
Please share and like this video.
Or join our membership
Protect your health with us
Which other type of oil would you like me to introduce?
Or food?
Leave a message and tell me.